Hello, learn German in Hindi,
welcome to this episode. There are a few
episodes in which we have definitely learned the conjunctions. In
total, we have learned 6 German conjunctions, 6 types of sub-conjunctions.
Which ones do we see? First of all, the simple
ones, after that, vile
and role, in the gym, work ends,
after that, 10 years ago, Priyanshu
learned plus infinitive, after that we
learned from relatives, and this is my favorite concept, final
product, and NCC. So, all these came, did you
revise them? If you haven't, then
you should do that. All of these should be together, that's why
I have made a playlist, German Conjunctions
in Hindi. You can find all of these in it.
Okay, when you revise a little bit,
then you can take this test. In this,
I have made 15
questions on all these topics. Solve them calmly, electrical
fittings, whatever paths you find,
and that's why write that. Definition of waist is
not there, why don't you worship,
revise that topic, it will tell you only and one
good thing is trust me on  This will
always be useful to you whenever you are learning, not only that, but if
you have not used it after 3 months or 6 months, then you
can check it again, where will you see 15 questions from here,
now whatever is viral, you know the words
but there is a problem in secretly doing Dheeraj-2, but you should
go and do the same episode again, the net will help, with
this they were handover revision till liquid, ok
everyone had it, when you understand then you will
see these 15 questions on the screen, you
can pause half the screen and
solve them without cheating,
I hope that all of you have understood the questions, right now
we will all answer them together, first of all it is very
easy to identify and
during copy, that is why we do Urdu Prince's
tree, simple them, simple castor oil, live
cricket because it can play cricket, this
mask cricket and Ishq cricket, speed jhankar
came in the reason because the same registrar,
character right side pizza young and
till 128 pass, this pizza boy Spain will again
in place of 'I' you can use
that IPL cricket made ball love lagz
request vanish in the here I
deliberately did a little nominated for
creativity not much for you right now we will go chukked
infinitive kids important
to learn German like this twist this otherwise oo
learn on I have no time to
meet mar this week's inner side March 253
tried to learn Spanish on this joker
Spanish London British now let's see the
market comment will rotate the market one and a half
love par heavy
that Anita Yadav am dead mic take Anita easy
effect meet patient again minute looted
yes highlight God and fry play football this
mask with Pushpa yellow flower closed year
sentence ka part bana banega ab last 5 my
favourite stars ko restaurant I drink
water Lipsy words
start ironing it mutual fights
that they can play I when cricket and football
veer wicket order some rain addiction I want to
drink 930 job woolen waiter's
notification tomorrow very simple right now  Swaad our
and from here from this inside oil pasta time math
pizza door Maa Pushpa side issues page
number claim make the sentence text condition
festival and collector is and one hand they want to
play cricket trap the other hand he must learn
German anal sex with strict channel its
India channel ka a
exactly like I said if you
want then you can write your marks in the comment section below if you get
good marks then it is a very
good thing but if you get less marks then don't worry about it go and
remind whatever happened from your body very easy I hope
you liked this episode we will meet
in the next episode it is powerful